Dark Souls Remastered is the Dark Souls of re-releases
and today I'm going to beat it faster than anyone else ever
Yes, this is a Dark Souls lore channel,
the best one on the site according to
secret emails from YouTube,
but what if I told you I'm also a Dark Souls speedrunner?
I'd be lying
for now
I've decided to become the first person to speedrun Dark Souls Remastered
"Kilian, you weren't the first person."
They don't count!
Because they speedran the unmastered edition
and that's essentially doping
Still gonna beat their time though because I am a Dark Souls master
Prepare to be in awe of my expertise
It appears when they made the remaster, they didn't keep my skills
After my 15th restart, I think I need to find a way to get better at the game
The best way to improve at Dark Souls is to
GIT GOOD SCRUB NUB
Okeh... okeh...
I guess I'll do that then
Wow! Once you git good, this game is silly easy!
Let's do this
I have formulated a plan to get the world record
Gonna play naked
No... I'll get demonetized
Gonna have to buy pants
Don't know anything about weapons
Black Knight Sword
Looks bad,
made for fighting chaos demons
I'm only facing skeletons
Gonna drop this, will only slow me down
Ah! That's just unlucky.
The club might be a terrible weapon but it's light
I mean, one kilo of wood is, what,
ten times lighter than one kilo of steel
Bell Gargoyle is dead, and first bell rung!
How long did that take? ...
17 minutes....
So, about half the time
I usually have troubles with the Capra Demon
but with the club and the pants, it's really easy
Maybe when the bosses see someone looking like this,
they are caught off guard and are easier to kill
Blighttown used to be laggy and that made it awful
But now they have removed the lag, so it's
still awful
Should have removed the entire thing, made the game 7 times better
Peter Parker dead,
and second bell rung!
And the time is....
24 minutes. Ooh
Off to Sen's Fortress. I gotta hurry to get this world record
"Kilian, to get an official record,
you have to post a full speedrun.
Uncut."
Yeah, about that.
My plan is to threaten to sue anyone who says my video is fake
and also bribe people
This part is supposed to be hard
but the archers are intimidated by me because I'm not wearing a shirt
and I'm showing off my abs
Okay, one of the hardest bosses in the game
How powerful is this club?!
Talked to the woman with the huuuuuuge pillow
And the time is...
30 minutes
I might not make it guys
I still have to get all the Lord Souls and defeat the final boss
First Lord is Seath
His place is very confusing,
but confusing is my specialty
(Sighs) No, you moron, this is not ice,
these are crystals!
That's why my character isn't freezing to death
Blue-Eyes White Dragon, it's time to duel!
Seath never took any life points
never even hit me
Like you, he was probably confused why my character wasn't freezing to death
Second Lord: a tree
What's the lore behind this tree?
There is none. It's just a tree.
To get to it, we have to travel through the Fire Kingdom
This remaster is the laziest remaster ever
except for fire
It's like management told everyone not to do anything
but forgot to tell the fire guy
The other big improvement: when you face Sif,
the cute dog, and his HP reaches 0,
he's fine, he just walks away backwards
The tree is the one boss where my overpowered club won't help
Not to worry, guys
Normal players fall down
but I have this boss attack down to milliseconds
I never claimed to be smart
GG, time for Nito, the boss I fear the most
Literally, because he's very spooky
Here goes
"Greetings and welcome, Undead.
Now, are you ready for
thy karate exhibition?!"
Chop Chop Master Nito: haiiiiiiii chahhhhh
Had to speed-rap that part
Now it's only the Four Kings left
that I am crushing
My god, the club and pants is the perfect Dark Souls combo
Guys, when the developers see this
I think they might remove pants
I have all the Lord Souls
How long did it take to beat all those bosses and mini bosses?
2 minutes
Good thing I invested all those points in stamina
to make me faster
I'm gonna get the record! I only have one boss left
Where is he?
I found a talking mushroom...
I am completely lost
I'm back in the game! And honestly,
I've played through the entire game using the first weapons so
I have to ask,
should Dark Souls have a hard difficulty?
Time for Gwyn
the guy from the intro
and what's the time?
Oh shit!
And he's so hard!
Damn that was hard
Reach the fire and
time!
I did it!
I beat the record!
I am officially the best Dark Souls player in the history of the universe
probably
It took 4 hours to beat this fucking boss with a club
Seriously, I have 4 hours of footage of just
running in this oversized ashtray